We missed the last bus
Did you know that?
He only gives me
one-word answers
and ignores me
like I'm not there
And that face…
Don't tell me…
Is he so mad
that I fell asleep
he won't talk to me?
He's the one
who missed the bus
I get nervous
when I'm around him
This won't do
I need to change
my approach
Hey
Hyeon-wu
Lee Hyeon-wu!
Hey!
At least pretend
to listen!
Look me in the face!
You're completely
ignoring me
I need to make
a risky move
Of course, you won't know
until you try
Is it my fault
that we missed the bus?
Is it?
Is it my fault
you a**hole?
I don't care
if he beats me up
I just have to express
my opinion
That was
my biggest mistake
If I had stood up
to Hyeong-ju
I wouldn't have
to do something crazy
Sorry
Huh?
Staying up all night
like this
made me
overthink things
I'm sorry if you're upset
Huh?
Normally, I would've
just brushed it off
but seeing him angry
made me feel
anxious. But why?
It's like I don't want him
to hate me
He apologized
Does that mean
we're equal now?
Can I finally escape
Hyeong-ju's
bullying now?
Hey, Hong Il-tak
Take out
all the money you have